And now
Now
You want to turn the tables
Did you do all this today
just to sabotage the partnership
between the Gu and Su families
Partnerships are negotiable
But they shouldn't be built on lies
Much less use my marriage as a cover-up
Without the support of
the Su and Gu families
How far do you think you can go
At least not towards you anymore
Mr Gu
What you should worry about now
isn't how far she can go
Then what is it
It's whether your partners will
still trust you
after hearing this recording
Brother Chengze
Let's step down for now
I won't stop you from
choosing each other
But from now on
stop using my
concessions to save your own face
Let's go
Not continuing the wedding
This place isn't suitable
for vows anymore
Su Mingyao
how dare you
You said I couldn't live
without this engagement
Now watch closely
It's you I'm leaving